You gonna say somethin'
or what?
It's your time.
- What's he doin' here?
-
a friend of mine
just walked right by.
Heshie. He has a 3:00.
Yeah.
Yeah, baby.
Oh, yeah.
What the hell's goin' on?
Thunderstorms.
- Jackie?
- You smell it? That's rain.
Dr. Melfi, what the hell
you doin' to me?
Go back to sleep.
What are you doin' up?
You got school tomorrow.
Workin' on a high score.
Did your mother
go to bed?
Yeah. Where were you?
Yeah. Compactor went down
at barone sanitation.
Move over.
Ready?
Yeah.
Go. Watch out
for the ghosts.
Whoa!
This thing ain't
steerin' right.
Yeah, kickin' your butt.
So how things goin' with you?
How's school?
Dad, you have
to concentrate. New game.
Hey, no fair.
It's called a handicap.
- Come on. Stop. Stop.
- Kickin' your ass now.
One hand. Look at that.
I can't see. Ha, ha.
Get off! Ow!
Stop! Come on!
You lose.
Focus through distractions.
There's a lesson for ya.
I want you in bed in 10 minutes.
Andretti, you listenin' to me?
Good night, dad.
Good night.
Dr. Nathan, please
return to e. R. Bay five.
Where'd you park?
In the parking lot.
No one followed me.
Adriana, you wouldn't
know it if they did.
Oh, yeah, like tony soprano's
hidin' in my backseat.
You are so paranoid.
Bring the car right here.
I know. He's in disguise.
That could be him. Hey, tony!
Or maybe he's in the trash can.
Come out, come out,
wherever you are. Ow!
Let go of me!
It could be anybody anytime.
I don't even know if
it's tony who's after me.
Christopher,
you gave crystal meth
to hisdaughter.
Which i'm not sure he knows.
Look at my wrist.
It's all red.
I'm sorry! I am sorry!
But i got dragged out
to the fuckin' meadowlands
by my neck, mock execution!
What?
Nothin'.
No. What?
You don't want to know,
okay? Trust me.
No. What?
I heard the nurse say you made
number two in your pants.
Is that what happened?
Get the car! Please!
Can we just go to brendan's,
score some shit...
and find out what the fuck
is goin' on, please?
The moon. The full moon!
Brendan, let's go.
Wake up, man.
For the exact time.
The fool leaves
his door open.
I gotta pee.
Go for it.
Yo, einstein.
You should have seen me
at the hospital.
It took three nurses
to hold me--
you will understand and comply
with the following orders.
All security personnel are to be
equipped with silver bullets.
Those silver bullets are
to be blessed by a priest,
not in english, but in latin.
All passengers and personnel
are to be restricted
to their cabins...
with the doors
bolted and locked.
End of orders! Sir!
Yes, sir!
Take him below.
Yeah. Yeah. Uh- huh.
That's the message. Thanks.
Way to go, anth!
Here, in five, four,
three, two.
Yo. Yo, check it.
You think this is funny?
What? What's funny?
Yeah, i didn't do nothin'.
You beep me one more time,
you're gonna be sorry.
We don't know what
you're talking about.
"Your mother blows."
That's a real original message.
Yeah, maybe she does,
right, anth?
Yeah.
Oh, yeah? Then why'd
you scarf up all the doughnuts
she sent us at camp?
And you used to cry on her
shoulder,"i'm so homesick,
mrs. Piocosta!"
Why don't you shut up?
Have another doughnut,
ya fat fart knocker.
Oh, go on! Kill'im!
Yeah!
Oh, yes!
Dick wad!
Ass!
Hey! Break it up.
Break it up!
I want a five- minute
cooldown period right now.
See ya next week, doc.
Oh, mr. Dante,
you forgot something.
Oh, thank you, baby.
- Don't forget to keep flossing.
- You saved my life.
All right.
See you next week, all right?
Can i help you, sir?
Sir? Sir?
Oh, my god.
I'm having
second thoughts.
About?
This whole thing,
the whole arrangement.
Security.
I come here. I tell you things.
I don't know how safe it is.
I understand
your concerns.
But i told you what the ground
rules are. As long as i don't
hear anything incriminating--
you don't fuckin' get it.
Just my bein' here
incriminates me.
Somebody sees me, they tell
somebody else. All of a sudden,
i'm a celebrity!
I thought
we made some progress
of your narcissism.
Who are you?
Why is that so important
for you to know?
My mother told me
never to answer a question
with a question.
So, your mother
did teach you something.
If i asked you about your life,
who you talked to,
who you trust--
i'd have to take the fifth.
That's cute.
Oh! I--
i-- i'm sorry.
I wasn't aware of
what i was...saying.
I'm...sorry.
Hey, what are you
doing here?
Chris sent me to pick you up.
Chris? Why?
Did something happen?
Must be my dad, right?
Why else would chris send you?
Did brendan get my poem?
It's probably nothing.
Another search warrant.
He calls them the federal bureau
of annoying bullshit.
You told your old man,
didn't you?
You scared me. What happened?
This is me and adriana movin'
to florida'cause some puke
couldn't keep your mouth shut.
What are you talking about?
Seriously. Did brendan
say anything about me?
Get us outta here!
Get us out!
What did you tell your old man?
About the meth? You insane?
He'd have me beaten up!
Don't you get it?
This is serious!
Let go of me!
Listen--
stop this shit!
He's worried about you.
He's been asking where
you've been, you asshole!
I'm sorry if i hurt ya.
I hate my life,
being a soprano.
Hey.
Don't ever say you hate life.
That's blasphemy.
Fuck you.
Okay, let's go. Remember
like when you were little.
I'll buy you one of those
happy meals, all right?
Where the fuck are you?
This is a new shirt.
Your grandmother
bought you this shirt.
I find it in the trash?
It's a westport.
It's not even cool anymore.
What did you just say?
I got in a fight.
I hope it was worth it.
I hope you did as much
damage to his wardrobe.
Who with?
I didn't get caught.
No demerits.
Anthony, who?
Jeremy.
Jeremy piocosta? You spent
all that time together at camp.
I thought you were friends.
Well, if that's all
the information i'm getting,
i'm calling mrs. Piocosta.
No, ma, wait.
Ma, don't call.
I swear. You kids
are going to learn
the value of a dollar.
I'll wash your car.
You never put
any effort in.
I will. I promise.
I'll do it really good.
Just don't call.
I'll get the money.
Forty dollars, anthony.
I know, i know.
Ma!
How ya doin'?
What brings you here?
Remember that pastry place,
ferrara's?
Brought you
some macaroons.
Oh, they're too sweet.
What are you talkin' about?
They're your favorites.
The activities director, rosie,
says they're organizing
a trip to the city.
Dinner and a show.
And you don't wanna go.
I don't like
the people here.
You don't know the people here.
And that city.
Grown men soiling themselves.
- It's not like that anymore, ma.
- That giuliani.
Maybe we should just
stick to the field trip.
Mothers throwin' their babies
out of skyscraper windows.
You're always with
the babies out the windows.
I don't see you tryin' to mix
with the other ladies here...
or talk to the nice gents
i see walkin' around.
You're not makin'
the most of your opportunities.
What do you care?
Out of sight, out of mind.
We don't think like that,
not me or carm or the kids.
I wish the lord
would take me now.
I come here to get cheered up.
You think that's a mistake?
You bein' sarcastic?
You can't put
all your problems on me.
This is the most expensive
retirement community
in new jersey.
If you wanted to, you could be
happy here, but you're just
pissing it all down the drain.
What beautiful language
for your mother.
You want the macaroons?
I don't care.
Leave some out
for the lunatics.
Good- bye, ma.
They're saying
it might rain today.
Don't worry. I'll drive safe.
What the hell are you doing?
This place is an hour
from my office.
An hour?
What are you, a woman?
Get a bladder transplant.
My mother lives here.
It's not real
convenient for me.
It's not convenient?
I'm sorry.
Why don't we meet by your
precinct? The government would
love pictures of us together.
What do you got for me?
Here.
"Jennifer melfi, m. D."
Yeah. Her background,
daily routine.
And your personal
relationship
with her is?
None of your
fuckin' business.
You can't blame a guy
for tryin'.
What are you,
bored with your life?
Oh, yeah, sure.
Bustin' whores and junkies.
Plus, it's a super huge thrill
to pay two alimonies on
a $40, 000- a- year income.
I don't want her touched.
I don't want her bothered.
I just want to know
the who, when, why.
That's it.
Usual fee?
The knicks lost, lieutenant.
You're down two large.
Lay off the vig.
We'll see what kind
of job you do.
Okay. See you in a few days.
What ya got in the box?
Macaroons.
This is awful.
I can't deal with this.
What kind of god? Hmm?
Christopher!
Where you been?
What happened to you?
Brendan's dead.
What are you talkin' about?
The fish is in my pocket.
Brendan's brains are
floatin' in his bathtub.
Message job through the eye.
- Mo green special.
- Fuckin' uncle junior.
What are you talkin' about,
mo green?
In one, mo green's
eyes got too big
for his stomach,
so they put a small
caliber in his eye.
- Mikey palmice does their hits.
- In his glasses, you mean.
Glasses, eyes.
Why you quibbling with me?
I'm at the world trade center.
What are you doin'?
Mikey palmice is a made guy.
Cocksucker didn't have
the balls to do it himself.
Contracted fuckin' russians
and he killed my friend.
Our response should
suit the message.
Through the mouth
means the guy was a rat.
The eye is just how
francis framed the shot,
for the shock value.
Brendan didn't deserve this.
Don't try to talk me out of it.
You can't touch mikey.
Your fuckin' uncle's
pissin' on your head.
What do you expect me to do?
I'm on it. I know where
mikey's house is
over by route ten.
No. He tries to leave,
you break his other neck.
Nurse bradley,
you're wanted in e. R.
Hey, mr. G. Q.
Hey.
Got a ticket.
Yeah.
How ya doin', mikey?
How ya doin'--
son of a--
look.
Your suit's wrinkled.
Let me fix it.
- Ow!
- What are you screaming about?
Free alterations.
Ow! Ow!
Mr. Slick.
This is overdue.
You hear about
the chinese godfather?
He made them an offer
they couldn't understand.
You gonna stop this
before it gets out of hand?
- Not even a hello?
- I'm here'cause i love you
and i respect you.
Don't pretend
you're payin' me respect.
A son who throws his mother
in an asylum.
She lives like
apoverettoup there.
That's none
of your business.
Your friends-- they interfere
in my business. They expect me
to turn the cheek.
The truck and all that
was made good to you.
I'm sitting here like patience
on a monument, waitin' for
discipline to be handed down.
Your boys were warned,
and still they embarrass me.
I run my crew my way.
What you did was extreme.
Now you're my judge?
I answer to bigger people
than you, my friend.
Oh? Like jackie?
Wanna take this
to his deathbed?
That nephew of yours
we gave a high colonic,
uh, he earns good?
He's comin' up.
Okay.
He works for me now.
Excuse me.
Maybe he gives youagito
for a change.
You got some set of balls.
You know that?
Absolutely not.
I show you my hand,
and you slap it away.
What's the matter with you?
Why can't we talk like
adults anymore, hmm?
Out. Next time you come in,
you come heavy or not at all.
You don't mean that.
So by the time i get to take
the sergeant exam, of course,
the pay scale is frozen by law.
Why are we following
these people?
They grabbed a meal,
saw a movie, so what?
Lucky for you
they stopped off
at that package store.
- Yeah, i got a juice.
- Yeah, i can smell the potatoes.
Hey, listen, asshole.
Same make and model
left the scene of a triple
homicide on long island.
Stay fuckin' current.
So you broke it off with
the poorshlubafter a week?
I know. I feel for you males.
It's our goddamn fault
you don't know how to act.
Oh, admitting mistakes.
We tell you
to be more sensitive.
You join promise keepers.
We say get in touch
with your feelings.
You run off into the woods
in a loincloth, gunking yourself
with bear fat, beating a drum.
Hey, don't ruin my evening.
You know what i mean.
Sure. You want someone
who's sensitive to your needs...
but still decisive enough
for the occasional grope
in the closet.
Yeah. Something like that.
Oh, shit.
That's all i need.
We were going over
the speed limit?
I wasn't looking.
Pull over.
License and
registration, please.
Uh, i'm sorry, officer.
Did i do something wrong?
Detective.
You crossed a double line.
Have you been drinking, sir?
We had wine with dinner.
Step out of the car, please.
I don't believe this.
Just relax, randall,
and do what he says, okay?
I need you to walk
a straight line to me, sir.
Heel to toe.
Look, uh,
i applaud your vigilance,
but this is totally unnecessary.
All right? I'm a lawyer.
I know i'm under the limit.
Open the trunk, please.
What?
You want to search
my golf bag?
Open it!
I will not.
You ever hear
of probable cause?
Oh, yeah, that's
a real good legalese--
what?
Oh, you resisting arrest?
- Hey!
-
vin, will you fuckin'
cool it? Vin!
He can't do that!
Get back in the car!
He didn't do
anything wrong!
Ma'am!
Back in the car. Now.
Come on. Let's go.
I perceived what
i thought was a weapon.
What the hell's
wrong with you, vin?
Take him. D. U. I. ,
resisting arrest, assaulting
an officer. Do it now.
What's he--
do it!
Jesus.
Don't you touch me!
You got prime rib at home.
Don't be goin' out
for hamburgers.
What? What are you
talking about?
Randall! Randall!
I'll follow you!
I'm gonna call my lawyer, you!
Fuck you!
She's seeing a randall curtin,
tax lawyer.
He's lives at
1242 rennsalaer road.
He's divorced.
He's got two kids.
He's the country club type.
Not much in the balls
department, i might add.
What about her?
Her, the good doctor, she's
in her office at 8:00 a. M.
She leaves at 6:00.
She orders up a tuna sub
and a diet coke.
She's got a three- bedroom condo
in essex fells,
shops at pathmark.
She's divorced.
One kid, 19.
Outside of schmucko,
she don't get out much,
but she does see a shrink.
She what?
Yeah.
She sees a shrink once a week.
His name is elliot kupferburg.
Oh, fuck me.
Well, she don't fuck anyone
from what i can tell.
Well, it's not because
she don't got the goods.
She left her blinds up.
I got some of them
victoria secrettype snaps.
If you're interested.
A little of this?
Good enough then?
Yeah.
- You got any advil?
- What am i, a fuckin'
pharmacy now?
What you got on friday's game?
I got three bills on rutgers.
I don't solve
all your problems.
Thank you.
With a stapler? Wow.
I heard mikey had to
give up that nice suit.
Yeah?
He got too attached to it.
Michael palmice's been
a disease since he was five.
He had it comin'.
It don't make things
any easier though.
My uncle's a stubborn man.
Stubborn enough to go to war?
What kind of word is that?
There hasn't been a war
since the columbo thing.
Everybody decided.
No one's goin' to
the mattresses this day and age.
I got a top- of- the- line
posturpedic at my house.
Fuck it.
If jackie hadn't
gotten sick, none of this
would have happened.
When you're right,
you're right.
One of us captains gotta
step up. Lack of control at the
top is fuckin' up this family.
- That's true.
- You can say that again.
If the old man were here,
instead of in that cell
in springfield,
he'd say,"raymond,
this is your moment."
Go easy with
the grease gun, okay?
What?
You're the boy wonder.
Both him and jackie
had you picked from day one.
You got the age.
You got the seniority.
I also got an 18- year- old
with m. S. , okay?
I told nucci
i'd be doin' less, not more.
All due respect to your
crippled kid, you don't
want a wire up your ass.
You don't want the headache.
That's why you should be boss.
You're so fuckin' smart.
And it's
"physically challenged."
Absolutely.
Why don't we run this thing
like a council?
Larry, the old guys set this up
as a paramilitary organization.
We need a supreme commander
at the top, not the fuckin'
dave clark five.
Face it. You and junior
are gonna have to duke it out.
You gotta be boss.
Number one:
I love the man.
Number two:
He's got new york behind him.
Not for anything,
god bless your uncle, but he's
livin' in the wrong century,
and new york knows it.
You want it, t?
You'll get their okay.
It's the right thing.
It's inevitable.
I don't want no disturbance.
Hey, what's up?
Nothin'.
I bet you told your mom
what happened.
What are you, high?
Well, you owe me 40 bucks
for the shirt. The collar
was totally ripped.
You still owe me
for fourth of july.
Bottle rockets?
I paid for them.
Not for the m80s.
Remember? The ones
you blew up the frogs with.
- Oh, yeah.
That was pretty cool.
- Yeah.
Listen. Just give me the money.
- That thing was so gay.
I did you a favor.
- You're gonna do it.
Make me, fatty.
- Dick wad.
- Asshole.
Whoa!
Shithead.
Bitch-- come on.
Let's go, shithead.
- Let me go!
- Why? So i can
kick your ass again?
- I was kicking your ass.
- Nobody won. It was a draw.
The pit tomorrow, 3:00.
You gotta help me
with these cinch bugs.
They're killing my sweet corn.
Well, this blue stuff works
pretty well, and it's safe
for the environment.
I tried that.
You got any d. D. T. Back there?
Uh, that stuff's illegal.
It's been banned.
Maybe you got a surplus in the
back, you could go, you look.
I'll meet you back there.
Look, mr. Soprano,
if i could do
something, i would--
mr. Piocosta! Right?
How ya doin'?
Remember our boys went
to camp aheka together?
Of course. Tony.
How are ya?
Good. Good.
Your kid still got
that killer crossover dribble?
- Yeah, i guess so.
- That's gonna get him
a scholarship.
- So how's anthony?
- He's moody, you know?
For a kid that age,
you know?
It was nice seein' ya, tony.
Why don't we get together and
cook up some dogs for the boys?
Tony, i-- i don't even know
if these guys are close anymore.
Did anthony mention
anything to you?
I'll have carmela call joanie.
We'll get together.
- Linda.
That's great.
Tony, that's great.
I'll see you around.
Tony?
Yeah.
Oh, my god.
Tony?
I thought the medication
was supposed to help
your panic attacks.
It-- it does.
It's the first one in a while.
What does your therapist say?
He should increase your dosage.
He's got more degrees
than a thermometer.
Don't worry about it.
I'll take care of it.
Does your therapist
ask questions
about our marriage?
I know that personal
feelings are hard for you
to talk about.
Talk. That's
all we do is talk.
Carm, i'm gonna quit.
Did you bring
this up with him?
Yeah.
He knows. I guess.
Oh, shit. I forgot to take
my fuckin' prozac this mornin'.
It's up in the bathroom.
Can you get it?
I know with jackie sick
you're under
tremendous pressure.
But i feel if
the therapy didn't hurt,
it wouldn't be helping.
No, you don't understand.
That's why you're
in therapy. Because
i don't understand!
I'm telling you, tony,
if you give up now, i'm gonna
have to reevaluate things.
What is that, huh?
I got a very sensitive job.
I'm not an average joe
on the block.
I gotta spell it out for you?
It's our marriage, tony!
Therapy is
too much exposure.
Fine!
You live with
the results then!
What's that, a threat?
No, tony.
It's a rave review.
You get your own
fuckin' pills.
How long did the attack last?
About 30 seconds.
I was dizzy, out of breath.
That's it though.
I never lost consciousness.
Anything since?
I'm gonna write
a script for xanax,
just for a couple of days.
It'll get you over
this short- term stresses.
My uncle. He's got me in a box
where i gotta do something
i don't wanna do.
And then there's my mother.
I pay four grand a month
for this place,
and she acts like i'm an eskimo,
pushing her out to sea.
She's testing.
Same as your uncle.
Like little kids.
There's a good book about this.
I'll give you the name.
No, i read, i go right out.
It'sstrategies for
coping with elder family.
Can't fuckin' spank'em though.
Would it hurt you
to let your mother think
that she's still in charge?
You have children.
You know what they're like.
You know that sometimes it's
important to let them have the
illusion of being in control.
Chris, my man!
Surprised to see me?
Heard they took you
for a little ride.
Tour of the meadowlands.
Oh, yeah?
Heard you had
a little b. M. Out there.
- So you got my cut?
- They came and took it.
- Who?
- Junior soprano's boys.
They said you was out,
and it's they corner now.
- You let them do that?
- I don't argue too well
suckin' on a smith & wesson.
- You didn't beep me?
- Word on the street,
you out of commission.
Sorry, man. Business.
Chris, you know there's
no one i'd rather give
my ten points to than you.
It's all right.
It's not your fault.