You gonna say somethin'or what?
It's your time.
- What's he doin' here?-
a friend of minejust walked right by.
Heshie. He has a 3:00.
Yeah.
Yeah, baby.
Oh, yeah.
What the hell's goin' on?
Thunderstorms.
- Jackie?- You smell it? That's rain.
Dr. Melfi, what the hellyou doin' to me?
Go back to sleep.
What are you doin' up?You got school tomorrow.
Workin' on a high score.Did your mothergo to bed?
Yeah. Where were you?
Yeah. Compactor went downat barone sanitation.
Move over.
Ready?Yeah.
Go. Watch outfor the ghosts.
Whoa!
This thing ain'tsteerin' right.
Yeah, kickin' your butt.
So how things goin' with you?
How's school?
Dad, you haveto concentrate. New game.
Hey, no fair.It's called a handicap.
- Come on. Stop. Stop.- Kickin' your ass now.
One hand. Look at that.I can't see. Ha, ha.
Get off! Ow!Stop! Come on!
You lose.Focus through distractions.
There's a lesson for ya.I want you in bed in 10 minutes.
Andretti, you listenin' to me?
Good night, dad.Good night.
Dr. Nathan, pleasereturn to e. R. Bay five.
Where'd you park?In the parking lot.
No one followed me.Adriana, you wouldn'tknow it if they did.
Oh, yeah, like tony soprano'shidin' in my backseat.You are so paranoid.
Bring the car right here.I know. He's in disguise.
That could be him. Hey, tony!Or maybe he's in the trash can.
Come out, come out,wherever you are. Ow!
Let go of me!
It could be anybody anytime.I don't even know ifit's tony who's after me.
Christopher,you gave crystal methto hisdaughter.
Which i'm not sure he knows.Look at my wrist.It's all red.
I'm sorry! I am sorry!
But i got dragged outto the fuckin' meadowlandsby my neck, mock execution!
What?
What?Nothin'.
No. What?You don't want to know,okay? Trust me.
No. What?
I heard the nurse say you madenumber two in your pants.Is that what happened?
Get the car! Please!Can we just go to brendan's,score some shit...
and find out what the fuckis goin' on, please?
The moon. The full moon!
Brendan, let's go.Wake up, man.
For the exact time.
The fool leaveshis door open.
I gotta pee.Go for it.
Yo, einstein.You should have seen meat the hospital.
It took three nursesto hold me--
you will understand and complywith the following orders.
All security personnel are to beequipped with silver bullets.
Those silver bullets areto be blessed by a priest,not in english, but in latin.
All passengers and personnelare to be restrictedto their cabins...
with the doorsbolted and locked.
End of orders! Sir!Yes, sir!
Take him below.Take him below.
Yeah. Yeah. Uh- huh.That's the message. Thanks.
Way to go, anth!
Here, in five, four,three, two.
Yo. Yo, check it.
You think this is funny?
What? What's funny?Yeah, i didn't do nothin'.
You beep me one more time,you're gonna be sorry.
We don't know whatyou're talking about.
"Your mother blows."That's a real original message.
Yeah, maybe she does,right, anth?Yeah.
Oh, yeah? Then why'dyou scarf up all the doughnutsshe sent us at camp?
And you used to cry on hershoulder,"i'm so homesick,mrs. Piocosta!"
Why don't you shut up?
Have another doughnut,ya fat fart knocker.
Oh, go on! Kill'im!Yeah!
Oh, yes!
Dick wad!Ass!
Hey! Break it up.Break it up!
I want a five- minutecooldown period right now.
See ya next week, doc.
Oh, mr. Dante,you forgot something.Oh, thank you, baby.
- Don't forget to keep flossing.- You saved my life.
All right.All right.See you next week, all right?
Can i help you, sir?
Sir? Sir?
Oh, my god.
I'm havingsecond thoughts.About?
This whole thing,the whole arrangement.
Security.
I come here. I tell you things.I don't know how safe it is.
I understandyour concerns.
But i told you what the groundrules are. As long as i don'thear anything incriminating--
you don't fuckin' get it.Just my bein' hereincriminates me.
Somebody sees me, they tellsomebody else. All of a sudden,i'm a celebrity!
I thoughtwe made some progressof your narcissism.
Who are you?
Why is that so importantfor you to know?
My mother told menever to answer a questionwith a question.
So, your motherdid teach you something.
If i asked you about your life,who you talked to,who you trust--
i'd have to take the fifth.
That's cute.
Oh! I--
i-- i'm sorry.I wasn't aware ofwhat i was...saying.
I'm...sorry.
Hey, what are youdoing here?
Chris sent me to pick you up.Chris? Why?Did something happen?
Must be my dad, right?Why else would chris send you?
Did brendan get my poem?
It's probably nothing.Another search warrant.
He calls them the federal bureauof annoying bullshit.
You told your old man,didn't you?You scared me. What happened?
This is me and adriana movin'to florida'cause some pukecouldn't keep your mouth shut.
What are you talking about?Seriously. Did brendansay anything about me?
Get us outta here!Get us out!
What did you tell your old man?About the meth? You insane?He'd have me beaten up!
Don't you get it?This is serious!
Let go of me!Listen--
stop this shit!He's worried about you.
He's been asking whereyou've been, you asshole!
I'm sorry if i hurt ya.
I hate my life,being a soprano.Hey.
Don't ever say you hate life.That's blasphemy.
Fuck you.
Okay, let's go. Rememberlike when you were little.
I'll buy you one of thosehappy meals, all right?
Where the fuck are you?
This is a new shirt.
Your grandmotherbought you this shirt.I find it in the trash?
It's a westport.It's not even cool anymore.
What did you just say?
I got in a fight.I hope it was worth it.
I hope you did as muchdamage to his wardrobe.Who with?
I didn't get caught.No demerits.
Anthony, who?Jeremy.
Jeremy piocosta? You spentall that time together at camp.I thought you were friends.
Well, if that's allthe information i'm getting,i'm calling mrs. Piocosta.
No, ma, wait.Ma, don't call.
I swear. You kidsare going to learnthe value of a dollar.
I'll wash your car.You never putany effort in.
I will. I promise.I'll do it really good.
Just don't call.I'll get the money.
Forty dollars, anthony.I know, i know.
Ma!
How ya doin'?What brings you here?
Remember that pastry place,ferrara's?
Brought yousome macaroons.
Oh, they're too sweet.
What are you talkin' about?They're your favorites.
The activities director, rosie,
says they're organizinga trip to the city.
Dinner and a show.
And you don't wanna go.
I don't likethe people here.You don't know the people here.
And that city.Grown men soiling themselves.
- It's not like that anymore, ma.- That giuliani.
Maybe we should juststick to the field trip.
Mothers throwin' their babiesout of skyscraper windows.
You're always withthe babies out the windows.
I don't see you tryin' to mixwith the other ladies here...
or talk to the nice gentsi see walkin' around.
You're not makin'the most of your opportunities.What do you care?
Out of sight, out of mind.
We don't think like that,not me or carm or the kids.
I wish the lordwould take me now.
I come here to get cheered up.You think that's a mistake?
You bein' sarcastic?
You can't putall your problems on me.
This is the most expensiveretirement communityin new jersey.
If you wanted to, you could behappy here, but you're justpissing it all down the drain.
What beautiful languagefor your mother.
You want the macaroons?
I don't care.
Leave some outfor the lunatics.
Good- bye, ma.
They're sayingit might rain today.
Don't worry. I'll drive safe.
What the hell are you doing?
This place is an hourfrom my office.An hour?
What are you, a woman?Get a bladder transplant.My mother lives here.
It's not realconvenient for me.
It's not convenient?I'm sorry.
Why don't we meet by yourprecinct? The government wouldlove pictures of us together.
What do you got for me?
Here.
"Jennifer melfi, m. D."Yeah. Her background,daily routine.
And your personalrelationshipwith her is?
None of yourfuckin' business.
You can't blame a guyfor tryin'.
What are you,bored with your life?Oh, yeah, sure.
Bustin' whores and junkies.
Plus, it's a super huge thrillto pay two alimonies ona $40, 000- a- year income.
I don't want her touched.I don't want her bothered.
I just want to knowthe who, when, why.That's it.
Usual fee?
The knicks lost, lieutenant.You're down two large.
Lay off the vig.We'll see what kindof job you do.
Okay. See you in a few days.What ya got in the box?
Macaroons.
This is awful.
I can't deal with this.
What kind of god? Hmm?
Christopher!Where you been?
What happened to you?What happened to you?
Brendan's dead.What are you talkin' about?
The fish is in my pocket.
Brendan's brains arefloatin' in his bathtub.Message job through the eye.
- Mo green special.- Fuckin' uncle junior.
What are you talkin' about,mo green?
In one, mo green'seyes got too bigfor his stomach,
so they put a smallcaliber in his eye.
- Mikey palmice does their hits.- In his glasses, you mean.
Glasses, eyes.Why you quibbling with me?
I'm at the world trade center.
What are you doin'?
Mikey palmice is a made guy.Cocksucker didn't havethe balls to do it himself.
Contracted fuckin' russiansand he killed my friend.
Our response shouldsuit the message.
Through the mouthmeans the guy was a rat.
The eye is just howfrancis framed the shot,for the shock value.
Brendan didn't deserve this.Don't try to talk me out of it.
You can't touch mikey.
Your fuckin' uncle'spissin' on your head.What do you expect me to do?
I'm on it. I know wheremikey's house isover by route ten.
No. He tries to leave,you break his other neck.
Nurse bradley,you're wanted in e. R.
Hey, mr. G. Q.Hey.
Got a ticket.Yeah.
How ya doin', mikey?How ya doin'--
son of a--look.
Your suit's wrinkled.Let me fix it.
- Ow!- What are you screaming about?Free alterations.
Ow! Ow!Mr. Slick.
This is overdue.
You hear aboutthe chinese godfather?
He made them an offerthey couldn't understand.
You gonna stop thisbefore it gets out of hand?
- Not even a hello?- I'm here'cause i love youand i respect you.
Don't pretendyou're payin' me respect.
A son who throws his motherin an asylum.
She lives likeapoverettoup there.
That's noneof your business.
Your friends-- they interferein my business. They expect meto turn the cheek.
The truck and all thatwas made good to you.
I'm sitting here like patienceon a monument, waitin' fordiscipline to be handed down.
Your boys were warned,and still they embarrass me.
I run my crew my way.What you did was extreme.
Now you're my judge?I answer to bigger peoplethan you, my friend.
Oh? Like jackie?Wanna take thisto his deathbed?
That nephew of yourswe gave a high colonic,uh, he earns good?
He's comin' up.Okay.
He works for me now.
Excuse me.
Maybe he gives youagitofor a change.
You got some set of balls.You know that?Absolutely not.
I show you my hand,and you slap it away.
What's the matter with you?Why can't we talk likeadults anymore, hmm?
Out. Next time you come in,you come heavy or not at all.
You don't mean that.
So by the time i get to takethe sergeant exam, of course,the pay scale is frozen by law.
Why are we followingthese people?
They grabbed a meal,saw a movie, so what?
Lucky for youthey stopped offat that package store.
- Yeah, i got a juice.- Yeah, i can smell the potatoes.
Hey, listen, asshole.
Same make and modelleft the scene of a triplehomicide on long island.
Stay fuckin' current.
So you broke it off withthe poorshlubafter a week?
I know. I feel for you males.It's our goddamn faultyou don't know how to act.
Oh, admitting mistakes.
We tell youto be more sensitive.You join promise keepers.
We say get in touchwith your feelings.
You run off into the woodsin a loincloth, gunking yourselfwith bear fat, beating a drum.
Hey, don't ruin my evening.
You know what i mean.
Sure. You want someonewho's sensitive to your needs...
but still decisive enoughfor the occasional gropein the closet.
Yeah. Something like that.
Oh, shit.That's all i need.
We were going overthe speed limit?
I wasn't looking.Pull over.
License andregistration, please.
Uh, i'm sorry, officer.Did i do something wrong?
Detective.
You crossed a double line.Have you been drinking, sir?
We had wine with dinner.
Step out of the car, please.
I don't believe this.
Just relax, randall,and do what he says, okay?
I need you to walka straight line to me, sir.Heel to toe.
Look, uh,i applaud your vigilance,but this is totally unnecessary.
All right? I'm a lawyer.I know i'm under the limit.
Open the trunk, please.What?
You want to searchmy golf bag?
Open it!I will not.
You ever hearof probable cause?
Oh, yeah, that'sa real good legalese--what?
Oh, you resisting arrest?
- Hey!-
vin, will you fuckin'cool it? Vin!
He can't do that!Get back in the car!
He didn't doanything wrong!Ma'am!
Back in the car. Now.
Come on. Let's go.
I perceived whati thought was a weapon.
What the hell'swrong with you, vin?
Take him. D. U. I. ,resisting arrest, assaultingan officer. Do it now.
What's he--do it!
Jesus.
Don't you touch me!
You got prime rib at home.Don't be goin' outfor hamburgers.
What? What are youtalking about?
Randall! Randall!I'll follow you!
I'm gonna call my lawyer, you!Fuck you!
She's seeing a randall curtin,tax lawyer.
He's lives at1242 rennsalaer road.
He's divorced.He's got two kids.
He's the country club type.Not much in the ballsdepartment, i might add.
What about her?
Her, the good doctor, she'sin her office at 8:00 a. M.She leaves at 6:00.
She orders up a tuna suband a diet coke.
She's got a three- bedroom condoin essex fells,shops at pathmark.
She's divorced.One kid, 19.
Outside of schmucko,she don't get out much,but she does see a shrink.
She what?Yeah.
She sees a shrink once a week.His name is elliot kupferburg.
Oh, fuck me.
Well, she don't fuck anyonefrom what i can tell.
Well, it's not becauseshe don't got the goods.
She left her blinds up.I got some of themvictoria secrettype snaps.
If you're interested.A little of this?
Good enough then?Yeah.
- You got any advil?- What am i, a fuckin'pharmacy now?
What you got on friday's game?I got three bills on rutgers.
I don't solveall your problems.
Thank you.
With a stapler? Wow.
I heard mikey had togive up that nice suit.
Yeah?He got too attached to it.
Michael palmice's beena disease since he was five.He had it comin'.
It don't make thingsany easier though.My uncle's a stubborn man.
Stubborn enough to go to war?
What kind of word is that?
There hasn't been a warsince the columbo thing.Everybody decided.
No one's goin' tothe mattresses this day and age.
I got a top- of- the- lineposturpedic at my house.Fuck it.
If jackie hadn'tgotten sick, none of thiswould have happened.
When you're right,you're right.
One of us captains gottastep up. Lack of control at thetop is fuckin' up this family.
- That's true.- You can say that again.
If the old man were here,instead of in that cellin springfield,
he'd say,"raymond,this is your moment."
Go easy withthe grease gun, okay?What?
You're the boy wonder.Both him and jackiehad you picked from day one.
You got the age.You got the seniority.
I also got an 18- year- oldwith m. S. , okay?
I told nuccii'd be doin' less, not more.
All due respect to yourcrippled kid, you don'twant a wire up your ass.
You don't want the headache.
That's why you should be boss.You're so fuckin' smart.
And it's"physically challenged."
Absolutely.
Why don't we run this thinglike a council?
Larry, the old guys set this upas a paramilitary organization.
We need a supreme commanderat the top, not the fuckin'dave clark five.
Face it. You and juniorare gonna have to duke it out.
You gotta be boss.Number one:I love the man.
Number two:He's got new york behind him.
Not for anything,god bless your uncle, but he'slivin' in the wrong century,
and new york knows it.
You want it, t?You'll get their okay.
It's the right thing.It's inevitable.
I don't want no disturbance.
Hey, what's up?Nothin'.
I bet you told your momwhat happened.
What are you, high?
Well, you owe me 40 bucksfor the shirt. The collarwas totally ripped.
You still owe mefor fourth of july.
Bottle rockets?I paid for them.
Not for the m80s.Remember? The onesyou blew up the frogs with.
- Oh, yeah.That was pretty cool.- Yeah.
Listen. Just give me the money.
- That thing was so gay.I did you a favor.- You're gonna do it.
Make me, fatty.
- Dick wad.- Asshole.
Whoa!
Shithead.
Bitch-- come on.
Let's go, shithead.
- Let me go!- Why? So i cankick your ass again?
- I was kicking your ass.- Nobody won. It was a draw.
The pit tomorrow, 3:00.
You gotta help mewith these cinch bugs.They're killing my sweet corn.
Well, this blue stuff workspretty well, and it's safefor the environment.
I tried that.You got any d. D. T. Back there?
Uh, that stuff's illegal.It's been banned.
Maybe you got a surplus in theback, you could go, you look.I'll meet you back there.
Look, mr. Soprano,if i could dosomething, i would--
mr. Piocosta! Right?How ya doin'?
Remember our boys wentto camp aheka together?
Of course. Tony.How are ya?Good. Good.
Your kid still gotthat killer crossover dribble?
- Yeah, i guess so.- That's gonna get hima scholarship.
- So how's anthony?- He's moody, you know?
For a kid that age,you know?
It was nice seein' ya, tony.
Why don't we get together andcook up some dogs for the boys?
Tony, i-- i don't even knowif these guys are close anymore.
Did anthony mentionanything to you?
I'll have carmela call joanie.We'll get together.
- Linda.- Linda.
That's great.Tony, that's great.
I'll see you around.
Tony?
Yeah.Oh, my god.
I thought the medicationwas supposed to helpyour panic attacks.
It-- it does.It's the first one in a while.
What does your therapist say?He should increase your dosage.
He's got more degreesthan a thermometer.
Don't worry about it.I'll take care of it.
Does your therapistask questionsabout our marriage?
I know that personalfeelings are hard for youto talk about.
Talk. That'sall we do is talk.
Carm, i'm gonna quit.
Did you bringthis up with him?Yeah.
He knows. I guess.
Oh, shit. I forgot to takemy fuckin' prozac this mornin'.
It's up in the bathroom.Can you get it?
I know with jackie sickyou're undertremendous pressure.
But i feel ifthe therapy didn't hurt,it wouldn't be helping.
No, you don't understand.
That's why you'rein therapy. Becausei don't understand!
I'm telling you, tony,if you give up now, i'm gonnahave to reevaluate things.
What is that, huh?
I got a very sensitive job.I'm not an average joeon the block.
I gotta spell it out for you?It's our marriage, tony!
Therapy istoo much exposure.Fine!
You live withthe results then!
What's that, a threat?
No, tony.It's a rave review.
You get your ownfuckin' pills.
How long did the attack last?
About 30 seconds.
I was dizzy, out of breath.That's it though.I never lost consciousness.
Anything since?
I'm gonna writea script for xanax,just for a couple of days.
It'll get you overthis short- term stresses.
My uncle. He's got me in a boxwhere i gotta do somethingi don't wanna do.
And then there's my mother.
I pay four grand a monthfor this place,
and she acts like i'm an eskimo,pushing her out to sea.
She's testing.
Same as your uncle.
Like little kids.
There's a good book about this.I'll give you the name.
No, i read, i go right out.
It'sstrategies forcoping with elder family.
Can't fuckin' spank'em though.
Would it hurt youto let your mother thinkthat she's still in charge?
You have children.You know what they're like.
You know that sometimes it'simportant to let them have theillusion of being in control.
Chris, my man!
Surprised to see me?Heard they took youfor a little ride.
Tour of the meadowlands.Oh, yeah?
Heard you hada little b. M. Out there.
- So you got my cut?- They came and took it.
- Who?- Junior soprano's boys.
They said you was out,and it's they corner now.
- You let them do that?- I don't argue too wellsuckin' on a smith & wesson.
- You didn't beep me?- Word on the street,you out of commission.
Sorry, man. Business.
Chris, you know there'sno one i'd rather givemy ten points to than you.
It's all right.It's not your fault.